Don't know about a new data structure called Stack.
Consider you are browsing on the internet, on Google Chrome and you go to Google Dot com.
There is this back created and put the stack that it is a Google dot com in the first place.
Then you go to Google.
So we have inserted in the stack YouTube dot com.
Then you go to Gmail dot com.
So the stack, but Gmail dot com and then you press this back button.
So what happens?
It will take you through their Gmail.
So we have removed it from the stack that Gmail.
And now if we press again the back, we go to Google, how does this thing done?
OK.
It is by using a stack, so a stack is an abstract data type that holds an ordered linear sequence of
item in contrast to cue that we are going to see in the next couple of videos.
The new data type after Stack is Q, so a stack is a last in, first out structure.
It is a lethal structure last and first out.
We will see the examples and the next videos, so in a stack data structure, you can only access the
element on the top of the stack.
The element that was added last will be the one to be removed first.
OK.
Therefore, to implement this stack, you need to maintain a pointer to the top of the stack.
The last element to be added?
OK.
So these are the elements of the stack that are found on the stack, and the top of these elements is
the three.
So it is presented at the top of the stack.
OK.
So the first element that would be exit and the last element that it is inserted.
This is called first.
The last and first out.
The last element enters the stack.
It is the first element that will be going out of this stack.
OK.
We will learn about the push, so how to add their elements, and we will learn about up how to remove
the elements and other and other methods and other operation.